

#### **PROFILE**

Having 4.4 years of experience in developing web-based applications using MVC.NET, jQuery, Bootstrap, Angular and Entity Framework. Strong in Object Oriented Programming concepts. Flexibility and Adaptability in regards with new technologies and environments. Ability to work effectively with Global project teams. Excellent organizational ability in handling time critical and multi-tasking environment.

#### CONTACT

	ON LACT
	+1 (816)-663-4868
<b>&gt;</b>	murali.ofc@outlook.com
	in.linkedin.com/in/muralichukka
	https://chkrish9.github.io/Portfolio

# AWARDS-



Applause award (April 2018) – Deloitte



**PHOTOSHOP** 

Best coding award (September 2015) – HCL (India).

# SKILLS-**Client-side Technologies:** HTML 5 CSS<sub>3</sub> SASS **BOOTSTRAP JAVASCRIPT JQUERY** ANGULAR 1.x ANGULAR 2.x Mobile Technologies: **IONIC 3** Server Technologies: **MVC.NET** C# **JAVA** Designing tools: **PENCIL**

# **MURALI KRISHNA SAI CHUKKA**

# **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

# **EXPERIENCE-**

2019

#### STUDENT DEVELOPER - UMKC

Maintaining college web applications. Developing the new enhancements according to the college requirements.

2017 - 2018

#### **BUSINESS TECHNICAL ANALYST - DELOITTE**

Responsibilities include Development, Unit testing, defect analysis, defect fixing, client interaction for clarification, maintaining the code quality and standards.

2014 - 2017 (

# **SOFTWARE ENGINEER - HCL**

Joined as a campus hire and finished training on Microsoft technologies. Worked as a full stack developer.

#### **EDUCATION-**

2018 - 2020

MASTER'S IN COMPUTER SCIENCE – PURSUING (Current GPA 4.0)
UNIVERSITY OF MISSOURI KANSAS CITY – USA (AUG 2018 – Present)
Specialization in Web Development and Data Science.

2009 - 2013

BACHELOR'S IN COMPUTER SCIENCE – 77.45 %

VELAGAPUDI RAMAKRISHNA SIDDHARTHA ENGINEERING COLLEGE - INDIA

Specialization in Web Development, Data Structures,

Software engineering development models.

# PROIECTS-

2018

# **FACTORY MAINTENANCE SYSTEM - UMKC**

- Implemented mobile application using ionic 3.
- Increased the performance of UI by storing static data like images, js files etc., on client-side database.
- Implemented Excel import functionality.

2017 - 2018

#### TECO ENERGY - DELOITTE

- Convert globalization functionality from resource files to database. Provided user interface in admin portal for translation.
- Design user interfaces for Agent portal.

2016 - 2017 (

#### PANASONIC MMS - HCL

- Redesigned entire application (74 web pages) using Bootstrap within a month.
- Implemented schedule back up of the database via web application.
- Increase the performance of the dashboard data by converting server-side code to stored procedures.

2015 - 2016

# PANASONIC WIP - HCL

- Setup base for the application using bootstrap and angularjs.
- Implemented dashboards using jsPlumb library.
- Implemented charts functionality in the application.

# 2014 - 2015

# **MEDTRONIC - HCL**

- Implemented a generic crud framework using bootstrap.
- Implemented import functionality.